Hello
friends, today we are going to talk about the Two
Times for Galaxy S5 Golden Rules,
so please watch this video completely and
see very carefully that there are many of my
videos and subscribers who say
that why we do 3210 splits and are
not losing weight, so today I will
tell you why you are not able to lose weight
and you are not following or using those five golden rules, so
hi everyone
I am Loafer and you were watching me at the
Tuk place, so you all are doing
good increase, I am absolutely fine and today I have
brought for you 500% clean lighting pack
of Two Times, if you
want to do anything for anything, then there are some rules for that thing, there is
some pattern, so Two
Times pre formula, sometimes there is a pattern, there are
five golden rules of it, if we
follow them, follow the rules and do it properly, then
we can also
grow weight very easily because I have done it, okay, it is very easy
and you can also do it,
very good, so friends, today's  The video
is very easy to understand in simple language,
I am going to
explain it to you very easily for ₹5 today
and then you will not have any problem in future
and those who say that look you are
using times of wool but it is
not having any effect, you will be able to find out where you are making a mistake,
let's
start the video, so friends, the
first golden rule of our three times before law is that
whenever you
sit with your food, the food should be
fresh, so this week it goes up
in the anar, so the balance is good, at least half an
anar, you will complete it,
not before that, what happens with us is that
whatever we eat, we eat it quickly
and make it fresh, I think I
keep it for 10 minutes or 15 minutes, I do
n't give more time than this, so its golden rule is that
we have to eat the food properly by
zooming three to two times, then
why would you tax the clock slowly  If
you eat slowly then the time will also be limited,
saving time does not mean that you should
sit with the food, you should keep thinking about it,
3232 white pink, it is
not like that, it is a packet that
when you sit with the food and you are eating roti
because there is no limit to the amount of food and
rice that you can eat, in this place you
sit with two rotis, but the food should be homemade,
okay, now send roti, vegetable, dal,
okay, you should send the stock of that roti,
whatever type you are taking, if you are four, then
come here, okay, if you want to lose weight quickly, then
if you have two mines, then come to one and
if you sit there, it will not be visible, that is
my promise, what you have to do is you have to
prepare this roti, put it on it, when you
feed the children, then break the roti into
small pieces, if you are behind this, then
you have to make at least six pieces in one roti, the
doctor will leave it aside,
okay,
while eating food there should not be any TV, phone or any
distraction,
Yours on time, but sit down, I made a point,
start slowly, start slowly, taste it, so do it,
okay, try every bite,
then fit it to times, let's come to this
golden rule of yours, so that golden rule which
we were just following, let's continue the
same further, so
our golden setting is that whatever
you have grinded, you have to
shave it very well, okay, you have to make
sure 3210, it will be a little difficult in the beginning,
but it will benefit you a lot in the future, if
you have problem of indigestion, then it will be fine,
if you have
acidity and gastric problem, then it will go away,
your weight will also reduce, along with that,
those who have problem of constipation, then
it will be fine, so in the beginning,
you will feel a little bit that how are you eating,
you may feel a little bit of pain too,
friends, but if you do that
and follow the rules, then
you will get used to eating like this very quickly,
I am sure that
Why do we have to do it 32 times only?
What will happen if you do it 30 times? You will
eat here, you have 116 pieces which will be finished easily,
when will we do the second roti, then there is
dal on it, there is vegetable also, you will
eat that in the same way, then it will be asked comfortably for half an hour, in a
mean style, our first
homework will be completed, by
getting control from it, our second will be
completed even better, there will be no distraction on anything, due to distraction, we do
not get the taste of the food in our hands, we do not
even know what we have eaten and
our stomach also does not get it properly, we swear,
okay, and the food has to be eaten properly, it goes and
rots in the stomach, due to which
indigestion happens, there are
diseases of a different nation, it does
not get converted into energy, it gets converted into fat
and we do it in the reverse calculation, okay, so
this is our second point, you
might have understood it well and many
people also do that why would they do anything, that is,
fast food 32 times, they will
eat biryani everyday, they will eat ice cream everyday,
then  So it is not possible then
it will not have that much effect you have to eat
your own food at home, whatever you eat should be home cooked food only then
it will be possible friends
come where you spend your ₹3 the third one is of
this type that you
mix the after half with your food, then
you have to take green tea, okay
so the 32 bar committee has
its own green tea, you can purchase it from there, otherwise
you
can also take any pre-packed cream, what does the pre-packed cream do,
it detoxifies the
body, whatever the pre-packed officer says, we take
out the useless things,
in simple words, if I tell you,
whatever impurities there are, they get out of that body,
toxins get out,
your body gets detoxified, it is
very good, it is also good,
okay what is your metabolism, it is
strong, if you take pre-packed tea,
okay then you have to take full
details, after you have done it, okay and
like last we have and  Discussed
why we have to do it 32 times and Pashtun was
that we have to complete the meal in half an anar,
so
what happens logically and scientifically is that our mind does it in
half and only after that it
gives the message that the stomach is full, only then
we get up, okay when your mind is full,
we feel that the stomach is full, that
signal reaches the mind only when it loses its temper
and by doing this we
complete the meal in 10 minutes,
what does Islam mean and if you are feeling hungry, you
can eat three rotis, four rotis, it
is okay with pain coming and going, but now if you eat comfortably then it is half,
you will have one roti in the meal, your
stomach will be filled well and you will have 37 points, so that is the
third point, this cream roll wheat,
you have to take green along with it,
in this side or in this formula you have to take the gland to get a
master's degree, okay, then
come those reports, golden rule,
Web, so like Muslim people ask that you get
stuck on it, you must be exercising because
I have done my around  I have lost 80 kgs of weight and it has become
advanced.
What happened in the beginning was that I lost only one kg of weight in eight days,
so it is a
big thing for me because I had a good
weight, now I would say that I have just become
slim and trim, I am fine now,
but I do not mean I must have become fat,
well, every height is a quarter, but
I also have to do it this way, now I have to lose
528 kgs and belly, and in the same way, when I
go to the canteen, whatever I
share with you, I did it two
times, people also ask me
that do you exercise, what do you do,
so I did not get time for exercise,
I used to walk, and this formula also
prevents you from getting tired throughout the day, you can get it everywhere on your phone, on your watch,
you can also download the app on your phone, how much did you
walk in the whole day, and this is not money for which
you are working, friend, there is
no cost account of anything, you mean you have to walk, you have to do it in the morning
or book it in Ease  If you want to have
dinner, turn it off,
and secondly, you have to walk nine steps, you can do this during the day as
well, then do some
in the morning and some at night or do an
innings, do it in which
setting, tell me what happens now, if I do it
vigorously the next day,
what happens with it is
that our body remains fit and
whatever we eat gets converted into energy and does
not get converted into fat, the
gallery matters, so the gallery, the
more deficit you set, it is
better to run the rare one, at that time turn it off,
now to turn it off you
can subscribe or you can blot it, it
seems to be a very good puja option, so
this is our fourth and golden rule, we come to
our first golden rule and this golden
rule is very much liked, I will
make many videos on this and you people
can go and see that if you want to lose weight in turmeric,
look at your skin, you
can see, okay, there is no left turn etc.,
absolutely how clean your skin is  And I have
washed this and
applied moisturizer, there is no problem, I
apply plastic, so when turmeric does its
tweet, your skin
remains the same, if you lose weight by staying hungry,
you do not eat anything, now I mean, you do
not take proper nutrition in all the things, then
what happens is that it affects the skin, it affects the
dark circles under the eyes,
sneezing and the condition of this gets worse,
so if you do not do this, I am doing it
correctly, those people who say that
right now your stomach is fine,
I am happy because it is gradually and right now
you can see from my previous video
Govinda is very real, so you can see that
I was sitting with Rafi, you said that a lot turmeric, according to that I
am fine and whatever you have
felt, turmeric has written exactly,
okay, my last point is that
software, you will have one bean and free day,
this can be said to be the best golden rule of this formula,
you do not have to remain soft the whole day
and I have
uploaded many recipes and videos of that,
so  If you see it there, it will be better
because this video will become very long. Okay, so
what to do in fennel day, you should
not take anything else. People who have hypertension
problem, whose BP is low, they should not do this.
Okay, now do not do it and avoid it.
And if you still want to do it, then
reducing the quantity of fennel is fine.
But this is some problem, some medical
stores have problems regarding tension, so I will suggest for them
that they should try this. Those
whose BP
remains extremely high, they can do it comfortably. This is the
half one and I have told you the rule, the
golden rule, try this.
In this, you should consume 2KG, 2.5KG, 1KG in a day only,
depending on the person, 2% of it gets
eliminated and goes away. It had gone to the local level
but the upper house has come back again. So if
you have lived for one and a half, how have you been, then it is
possible that your 500 grams or 10
grams may fall, it does not notice it. It
means that you have eaten something wrong, you have given something wrong to your
body.  That happens with me too,
it doesn't happen that much now, but the
setting used to be very less, when I used to do this trick, then
that butt and around it also used to increase,
sometimes I used to read advance, so that issue has gone to some extent,
and along with that, the fat on your body face,
which used to get destroyed, when I woke up in the morning,
my face was completely fat
and my body was VC, it was of no use at all, it gets
eliminated because
our water retention gets
eliminated, send a minute for recording, the
water that is accumulated, it all goes down,
okay, so these were our today's
golden rules of 32 times to
inform, and how did you like this video,
if you liked it, then please like and
share it with friends and family and
definitely subscribe to the channel, so let's
meet in the next video, the front
part is okay, Allah Hafiz